RG 071, Department of Housing
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Commissioner, 1979-1994; 25 cubic feet
  - Subject Files
    - John F. Papandrea, 1986-1990; 6 cubic feet
      - 1991-020, 5 cubic feet
        - Governor's Support services positions (Box 2)
        - Governor's Washington Office (Box 2)
        - Finacial statement (Box 2)
        - Hall neighborhood Housing (Box 2)
        - Hartford Pilot (Box 2)
        - Housing production calendar, 1987 July - 1990 January (Box 2)
        - Human resources (Box 2)
        - Internal Audits (Box 2)
        - Key issues Forum, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Lead Based paint, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Lease Request DOH (Box 2)
        - Legal unit (Box 2)
        - Legislative proposal, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Legislation (Box 2)
        - Long term care (Box 2)
        - Causey (Box 2)
        - MIP (Box 2)
          - Duffy (Box 2)
          - untitled, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Management division monthly report (Box 2)
        - Mental health (Box 2)
        - Meriden, Willow court (Box 2)
        - Merit Promotion system Auditor's report (Box 2)
        - Milford Housing, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Mobile and Manufactured Home advisory council, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Monthly status report (Box 2)
        - Mutual housing (Box 2)
        - Multi family housing (Box 2)
        - Notice of intent to adopt regulations (Box 2)
        - North Branford housing authority (Box 2)
        - NAHRO (CT Chapter) (Box 2)
        - National NAHRO (Box 2)
        - Naugatuck Housing Authority, 1987 (Box 2)
        - Naugatuck Commissioner (Box 2)
        - New Britain Housing Authority (Box 2)
        - Newsletters (Box 2)
        - Subpoenas (Box 3)
        - Team (Box 3)
        - Tenant particupation (Box 3)
        - St. Josephs college (Box 3)
        - Vacation schedules (Box 3)
        - Bill wheeler (Box 3)
        - Sal Zito's office (Box 3)
        - New Samaritan (Box 3)
        - OPM, 1987 (Box 3)
        - News clippings (Box 3)
        - Norwalk (Box 3)
        - Personnel (Box 3)
        - Program Development and evaluation unit (Box 3)
        - Press releases (Box 3)
        - Price waterhouse proposal (Box 3)
        - Regulations (Box 3)
          - rental subidy (Box 3)
          - affordable housing (Box 3)
        - Rental assistance program (Box 3)
        - Rental housing for the elderly (Box 3)
        - Represenatives- 34 positions (Box 3)
        - St. Jude's Congregate, 1987 (Box 3)
        - Section 8 Automation, 1987 (Box 3)
        - Small cities, 1987 (Box 3)
        - Wheeler Smith, 1987 (Box 3)
        - UCONN Survey (Box 3)
        - Yale Study (Box 3)
        - Spare Request (Box 3)
        - State Ethics Commission, 1987 April 10 (Box 3)
        - Status reports, Fiscal compliance (Box 3)
        - Supervisors' Meetings (Box 3)
        - Task Force to study septic system repair loans, 1987 (Box 3)
        - Time sheets (Box 3)
        - Traumatic Brain Injury, 1987 (Box 3)
        - Vernon street bus garage (Box 3)
        - Waterbury Housing Authority (Box 3)
        - Wetland Technical assistance condition task force (Box 3)
        - Ron william (Box 3)
        - Willow court, 1987 (Box 3)
        - Back-up material for commissioner's meetings, 1987 (Box 3)
        - Paul Bobbit (Box 4)
        - Ed Bobigan (Box 4)
        - Budget submission, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
        - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
        - Capitol Region Council of Governments (Box 4)
        - Channel 8 (Box 4)
        - Citizens Advisory Council for housing matters, Raphael Podolsky (Box 4)
        - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 4)
        - CAFCA CONF. Norwich Inn (Box 4)
        - CONN Association for human service-nomination (Box 4)
        - Connecticut housing partnership (Box 4)
        - Conn. Housing Investment Fund (Box 4)
        - Connecticut plan (Box 4)
        - Creative Housing (Box 4)
        - Day Berry and Howard (Box 4)
        - Directors Meetings (Box 4)
        - Dower Associates (Box 4)
        - Jack Dollard (Box 4)
        - Retreat, July 29 (Box 4)
        - Executive retreat (Box 4)
        - Fairfield University (Box 4)
        - Furniture (Box 4)
        - Gala Ball (Box 4)
        - Governor's Council on Voluntary Action (Box 4)
        - Governor's Conference on Aging, 1988 October 18 (Box 4)
        - William hernadez (Box 4)
        - Homeless info (Box 4)
        - Department of Health services (Box 4)
        - Housing Statistics in Ct. (Box 4)
        - Homelessness (Box 4)
        - HUD (Box 4)
        - Interview (Box 4)
        - Human Service cabinet (Box 4)
        - Job's for Connecticut's Future (Box 4)
        - Key issues (Box 4)
        - Legislators' correspondence (Box 4)
        - Legislative program review and investment (Box 4)
        - Legislative proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
        - Housing legislation, 1988 (Box 4)
        - Lucas Gardens (Box 4)
        - Mansfield Task force (Box 4)
        - David Mead (Box 4)
        - Mission and Goals of D.O.H (Box 4)
        - Negotiated Investment Strategy (Box 4)
        - Neighborhood reinvestment corporation (Box 4)
        - NHS-New Britain (Box 4)
        - Northern Conn. Community Dev. Corporation (Box 4)
        - Norwich Bulletin interview (Box 4)
        - Office of Fiscal Analysis (Box 4)
        - Office of Policy and management (Box 4)
        - Open Hearth (Box 4)
        - Jean Pottinger (Box 4)
        - Press releases (Box 4)
        - Prime (Box 4)
        - unlabeled (Box 4)
        - Reorganization, 1987 (Box 4)
        - Reports (Box 5)
        - RAP status report file (Box 5)
        - Responses to internal operations review (Box 5)
        - The Royal (Box 5)
        - Small cities program (Box 5)
        - Administrative services (Box 5)
        - Application review comm. (Box 5)
        - Frank Dejesus (Box 5)
        - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
        - Capital Funds, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
        - Flex funds, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
        - Employee training (Box 5)
        - Monthly Appropriations, 1988 (Box 5)
        - Administration, Jeanne Wischenbar (Box 5)
        - Administrative services (Box 5)
        - Affirmative action (Box 5)
        - Single audit account (Box 5)
        - Affordable Housing (Box 5)
        - Attorney General (Box 5)
        - Blue ribbon commission (Box 5)
        - Blue ribbon commission (Box 5)
        - Budget (Box 5)
          - General Fund Secretary Milano (Box 5)
          - General Fund financial status, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
          - untiltled, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
        - Certificate of Term ination (Box 5)
        - CHA (Box 5)
        - Cofranesco, Richard (Box 5)
        - Congregate - elderly (Box 5)
        - Mary Lou Crane (Box 5)
        - Rob Cook (Box 5)
        - Cook, Automation Study (Box 5)
        - Rob Cook (Box 5)
        - Community Land Trust, Norwalk (Box 5)
        - James Conklin, Conventional Loans (Box 5)
        - CRCOG (Box 5)
        - DWD, Four day work wee (Box 5)
        - David W. Deakin, Miscellaneous (Box 5)
        - Dedications (Box 5)
        - Detroit visit (Box 5)
        - Director's meeting (Box 5)
        - Directors, Weekly activity report (Box 5)
        - Director's meeting, minutes (Box 5)
        - DOH (Box 5)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
          - untiltled (Box 5)
          - Program production (Box 5)
          - Proposed policy (Box 5)
          - General letters (Box 5)
        - Downpayment assistance program, Richard Cofrancesco (Box 5)
        - Dower Associates, Retreat (Box 5)
        - DOH, New proposals (Box 5)
        - Pat Downs, Planning (Box 5)
        - DOH, Policies (Box 5)
        - Downpayment assistance (Box 5)
        - Duffy, Michael T. (Box 5)
        - Energy conservation, Loan program (Box 5)
        - Energy conservation, Loan program (Box 5)
        - Escalera, Yasha (Box 5)
        - Executive group, 1988 September 26 (Box 5)
        - Executive retreat, Responses (Box 5)
        - FAC (Box 5)
        - Family Housing (Box 5)
        - Forms (Box 5)
        - Fusaro, Ted (Box 5)
        - Governor (Box 5)
          - Information line (Box 5)
          - William A. O"Neill (Box 5)
        - Harrel Avenue, Affordable (Box 5)
        - Harrity, David, Management (Box 5)
        - Hayes, Personnel and Training section (Box 5)
        - Hayes, Sheila (Box 5)
        - Homeless program (Box 5)
        - Housing authorities (Box 5)
        - Hudson, Fleeta (Box 5)
        - Human Services cabinet (Box 5)
        - Insurance (Box 5)
        - Internal Auditor (Box 5)
        - INTI (Box 5)
        - Insurance Liability (Box 5)
      - 1992-011, 1 cubic foot
        - Correspondence, 1988 February-1989 March (Box 1-2)
        - Marcy Lou Crane, Executive Assistant, correspondence, 1987 October-1989 January (Box 2)
        - James A. Petit, Executive Assistant, correspondence, 1988 July-1988 November (Box 2)
    - Henry S. Scherer, 1990-1994; 1995-032; 6 cubic feet
      - Commissioner Correspondence, Letters and Memos, 1991 (Box 1)
      - Governor's Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
      - Commissioner Correspondence, 1992 October - 1993 December (Box 2)
      - Commissioner Correspondence, 1992 January - 1993 September (Box 3)
      - Memos, 1992-1994 (Box 4)
      - Legislator's Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
      - Governor's Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 4)
      - Memos and letters; incoming and outgoing, 1991-1994 (Box 5)
      - Governors Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 5)
      - Legislator's Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 5)
      - HUD Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 5)
      - Affirmative Action, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Audit, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Delegation of Authority, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Economic Information system steering committee, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Edwards, A.G. and Sons, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Edwards, J.D., 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Elton Hotel, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Emergency Assistance Mortgage Program, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Gary, Albert - AEG, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Hall - Brook Foundation, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Houle File, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Inservice Training, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Inter-agency Committee on Youth Violence, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
      - Inter-agency Workgroup, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
    - Executive Assistant Bob Hardiman, 1983-1987; 1989-008; 2 cubic feet
      - Housing Starts (Box 33)
      - Governor's Day Aging (Box 33)
      - Freedom of information (Box 33)
      - Federal budget (Box 33)
      - Graph for bills (Box 33)
      - Ground breaking, dedication (Box 33)
      - Handicapped (Box 33)
      - Help wanted, 1984 December (Box 33)
      - Home Builders (Box 33)
      - Connecticut conference of Munis (Box 33)
      - Design covers (Box 33)
      - Governor activity report (Box 33)
      - Commissioner dates, speeches (Box 33)
      - illegable folder (Box 33)
      - Building renovations (Box 33)
      - Birthday, 350th (Box 33)
      - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority (Box 33)
      - Congregate (Box 33)
      - Contractors, illeagal (Box 33)
      - Chief energy AD. (Box 33)
      - Bonding (Box 33)
      - Bond commission, 1984-1985 (Box 33)
      - Administrative expenses (Box 33)
      - Auditors, 1983 (Box 33)
      - Auto records (Box 33)
      - Danbury, pilot (Box 33)
      - Greenwich, pilot, 1987 April 24 (Box 33)
      - Tax abatement, Hartford (Box 33)
      - Rehab $237,000 WTBY, 1987 April 23 (Box 33)
      - Pilot, Wethersfield, Darien (Box 33)
      - Meriden, $115,000 Rent Subsidy Southington, Rehab grant, Plainville rehab grant, 1987 April 15 (Box 33)
      - Pilot Meriden, Stamford, Norwich (Box 33)
      - Untitled folder (Box 33)
      - Untitled folder (Box 33)
      - Untitled folder (Box 33)
      - Clubs and organizations (Box 33)
      - Commissioner signuature required (Box 33)
      - Single purposed small city grants (8) cities (Box 33)
      - BIOG, Commissioner Papandrea (Box 33)
      - Small Cities, 2nd year grant seven cities (Box 33)
      - East hartford, Pilot (Box 33)
      - Quarterly Housing Report, M.I.S., 1986 March 31 (Box 33)
      - Untitled folder (Box 33)
      - Untitled folder (Box 33)
      - Governor monthly reports (Box 33)
      - Implementation 3 year plan (Box 34)
      - Legislator's, 1985 (Box 34)
      - Letters, replies (Box 34)
      - M.T.P. (Box 34)
      - Newspaper Ads (Box 34)
      - Newsletter and mailing list (Box 34)
      - P.I.L.O.T. (Box 34)
      - Rent subsidy study (Box 34)
      - Rent limits, income (Box 34)
      - Small business, set aside (Box 34)
      - Section 8 subsidy (Box 34)
      - Small city cover (Box 34)
      - Security loans (Box 34)
      - Legislation, 1985 (Box 34)
      - D.O.H. Programs and projects (Box 34)
      - OLR to P and D reports (Box 34)
      - Untitled folder (Box 34)
      - Weatherization (Box 34)
      - Wage Rates, federal and State (Box 34)
      - Untitled folder (Box 34)
- Series 2. Deputy Commissioner, 1978-1990; 38 cubic feet
  - Subject Files
    - David W. Deakin, 1978-1988; 1989-008; 21 cubic feet
      - Log records (Box 12)
      - Correspondence (Box 13)
        - CHFA meetings, 3 inches (Box 13)
        - Administration, miscellaneous reports (Box 13)
        - Administration, 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Afirmative Action Advisory Committee (Box 13)
        - Affirmative Action (Box 13)
        - Attorney General (Box 13)
        - Untitled folder, 2 inches (Box 13)
        - CHFA annual operating plan, review and correspondence (Box 14)
        - Canale, Joseph E., Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 14)
        - Miscellaneous DOH Correspondence (Box 14)
        - Deakin, David W. (Box 14)
          - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 14)
          - Out Letters (Box 14)
        - Personnel matters (Box 14)
        - CHFA (Box 15)
        - CHFA (Box 16)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, D.W.D, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
        - CHFA meetings, 7 inches (Box 16)
        - CHFA, Correspondence, memos, ect. (Box 16)
      - Section 8, Relocation File (Box 17)
        - Organization charts, 3 inches (Box 17)
        - Rent subsidy Inter agency (Box 17)
        - Rental rehab (Box 17)
        - Section 8, 1987; 4 folders (Box 17)
        - Rental assistance program (Box 17)
        - Small cities, 1984 (Box 17)
        - Relocation (Box 17)
      - Affirmative Action Town Plans (Box 18)
        - Legislative material, 3 inches (Box 18)
        - Housing Authority of the City of (Box 18)
          - Ansonia (Box 18)
          - Berlin (Box 18)
          - Branford (Box 18)
          - Bristol (Box 18)
          - Canton (Box 18)
          - Danbury (Box 18)
          - Darien (Box 18)
          - East Hampton (Box 18)
          - East Windsor (Box 18)
          - Ellington (Box 18)
          - Enfield (Box 18)
          - Fairfield (Box 18)
          - Farmington (Box 18)
          - Glastonbury (Box 18)
          - Greenwich (Box 18)
          - Griswold (Box 18)
          - Groton (Box 18)
          - Guilford (Box 18)
          - Hamden (Box 18)
          - Hartford (Box 18)
          - Killingly (Box 18)
          - Lisbon (Box 18)
          - Litchfield (Box 18)
          - Manchester (Box 18)
          - Meriden (Box 18)
          - Middletown (Box 18)
          - Milford (Box 18)
          - Montville (Box 18)
          - Naugatuck (Box 18)
          - New Britain (Box 18)
          - New Canaan (Box 18)
          - New Haven (Box 18)
          - Newington (Box 18)
          - North Branford (Box 18)
          - Norwalk (Box 18)
          - Norwich (Box 18)
          - Plainville (Box 18)
          - Plymouth (Box 18)
          - Portland (Box 18)
          - Preston (Box 18)
          - Putnam (Box 18)
          - Rockville, 3 folders (Box 18)
          - Simsbury (Box 18)
          - Southington (Box 18)
          - Stamford (Box 18)
          - Stratford (Box 18)
          - Seymour (Box 18)
          - Shelton (Box 18)
          - Thompson (Box 18)
          - Tolland (Box 18)
          - Torrington (Box 18)
          - Wallingford (Box 18)
          - Waterbury (Box 18)
          - West Hartford (Box 18)
          - Westport (Box 18)
          - Wethersfield (Box 18)
          - Willimantic (Box 18)
          - Windsor (Box 18)
          - Windsor Locks (Box 18)
        - Redevelopment Agency (Box 18)
          - Ansonia (Box 18)
          - Bridgeport (Box 18)
          - Danbury (Box 18)
          - Enfield (Box 18)
          - Glastonbury (Box 18)
          - Middletown (Box 18)
          - New Britain (Box 18)
          - New Haven (Box 18)
          - New London (Box 18)
          - Norwich (Box 18)
          - Putnam (Box 18)
          - Stamford (Box 18)
          - Stratford (Box 18)
          - West Haven (Box 18)
          - Willimantic (Box 18)
      - Bureau of housing, skills survey (Box 18)
      - Newington, Children's center (Box 18)
      - Newtown's Day care center (Box 18)
      - Waterbury Urban renewal (Box 18)
      - Construction activity reports, .5 inch (Box 19)
      - COSCAA (Box 19)
      - Liebson, Alice R., Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 19)
      - Log items (Box 19)
      - Sharpe, Michael M, miscellaneous (Box 19)
      - Shealy, Marin J., Commissioner, DOA (Box 19)
      - Three year plan, 1980 (Box 19)
      - Subject Files (Box 20)
        - Administration Temporary file (Box 20)
        - Administration reports (Box 20)
        - Minority contractors, Affirmative action (Box 20)
        - Alder house (Box 20)
        - Architect's contract revision (Box 20)
        - Attorney general, blue ribbon commission (Box 20)
        - Single audit report, 1985 June (Box 20)
        - Augustana Homes, Bethel congregate project (Box 20)
        - Beardsley Terrace and Pequonnock meeting minutes, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Beechwood Gardens, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Bergin, Sandy, Jean Claude L., Simonson properties (Box 20)
        - Bids (Box 20)
        - Bloomfield A.C.C. (Box 20)
        - Bond Commission, 1988; 11 folders (Box 20)
        - Brandford Housing Authority (Box 20)
        - Bridgeport affordable Housing Program (Box 20)
        - Bridgeport Roberto clemente, HSD (Box 20)
        - Bridgeport, Housing program (Box 20)
        - Broad/ Lawrence (Box 20)
        - Building codes and standards, national (Box 20)
        - Budget, 2 inches (Box 20)
        - Budgeted expenses federal funds, 1st quarter, 1983-1984 (Box 20)
        - Budget Bonding requests (Box 20)
        - Budget, federal (Box 20)
        - Capital budget requests, 1983-1984 (Box 20)
        - Capitol Housing corporation (Box 20)
        - Central Housing committee (Box 20)
        - C.H.A., 1987 (Box 20)
        - C.H.A., 3 inches (Box 21)
        - Chauncey Harris (Box 21)
        - CHIF (Box 21)
        - Citi Bank Proosal (Box 21)
        - Citizens for effective governrment (Box 21)
        - Civil preparedness (Box 21)
        - Claims (Box 21)
        - Clay Hill (Box 21)
        - Coalition of New England Governors (Box 21)
        - Comptroller (Box 21)
        - Bureau of codes and standards (Box 21)
        - Action Housing (Box 21)
        - A-95 (Box 21)
        - Condo regulations (Box 21)
        - Condominium conversions (Box 21)
        - Congregate Workshop (Box 21)
        - Congregate, 3 inches (Box 21)
        - DOT Land for Housing (Box 21)
        - Congregate C.H.A. (Box 21)
        - Congregate Housing, Task Force (Box 21)
        - Congregate costs, services (Box 21)
        - Connecticut Rural development council (Box 21)
        - Construction activity, housing starts (Box 21)
        - Construction and Maintenance section supervisior, EXAM (Box 21)
        - Contracts/applications (Box 21)
        - Copying Machine, Fifth Floor (Box 21)
        - Corp. For independent living (Box 21)
        - Coscaa (Box 21)
        - CRCOG (Box 21)
        - CSEA (Box 21)
        - Director's meetings (Box 21)
        - DOH Regulations (Box 21)
        - DOH sunset, 1983 (Box 21)
        - Long range data processing planning (Box 21)
        - David Deakin (Box 21)
        - Travel, 3 inches (Box 21)
        - DOH Audits (Box 21)
        - DOH, Accomplishments (Box 22)
        - Donen, Steve (Box 22)
        - Downpayment Assistance Program (Box 22)
        - DOH Regulations (Box 22)
        - Duffy, Michael T., Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 22)
        - Elderly (Box 22)
          - congregate Programs (Box 22)
          - Housing Income Limits (Box 22)
          - M.R. Rehab (Box 22)
          - projects and planning (Box 22)
          - closeouts (Box 22)
          - Housing, general conditions (Box 22)
          - Housing, vacancy survey (Box 22)
          - Meetings, standards for elderly rental homes (Box 22)
        - Connecticut energy foundation (Box 22)
        - Energy programs (Box 22)
        - Energy Loans (Box 22)
        - DP Planning, phases of (Box 22)
        - Disaster assistance (Box 22)
        - Disaster funds, Windsor Tornado (Box 22)
        - DOH insurance (Box 22)
        - General letters (Box 22)
        - General statutes (Box 22)
        - Governor's Housing coordinating council (Box 22)
        - Governor's conference on aging (Box 22)
        - Elderly Housing (Box 22)
        - El Hogar, 1984 (Box 22)
        - Ellington small cities application (Box 22)
        - Emergency fuel assistance program (Box 22)
        - Emergency Housing (Box 22)
        - Energy audit (Box 22)
        - Energy conservation loan program (Box 22)
        - Energy conservation (Box 22)
        - Federal prepayments (Box 22)
        - Hartford Housing Authority, sewer use, David W. Deakin (Box 22)
        - Hartford Pilot (Box 22)
        - City of Hartford (Box 22)
        - Hearthstone Apts, Bridgeport (Box 22)
        - HSD, Program, HDC (Box 22)
        - Executive order one (Box 22)
        - FAC (Box 22)
        - Fairfield Housing Authority, proposed M.R. (Box 22)
        - Fairmount Heights (Box 22)
        - Federal Audit (Box 22)
        - Federal Budget reductions impact on DOH Programs (Box 22)
        - FEMA, Mobile Homes, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Field support and maintenance MR and Elderly status reports (Box 22)
        - Finance advisory committee (Box 22)
        - Finance committee session, 1980 (Box 22)
        - Finance and Bonding Committee (Box 22)
        - Five year plan (Box 22)
        - Flex, time (Box 22)
        - FNMA (Box 22)
        - Freedom of Information act, 1980 December (Box 22)
        - Flood relief, special legislative session, 1982 (Box 23)
        - General assembly (Box 23)
        - Coverage Governor's info (Box 23)
        - Governor O"Neill (Box 23)
        - DOH, CHFA, Yankee Mac, Governor's campaign (Box 23)
        - Governor O"Neill, Bi-weekly report (Box 23)
        - Governor's Task Force on Regulatory reform (Box 23)
        - Gramm, Rudman, Hallings (Box 23)
        - Greater Hartford Jewish Federation (Box 23)
        - Housing, State of Connecticut regulation of the department of (Box 23)
        - Handicapped Housing (Box 23)
        - Hartford Pilot (Box 23)
        - Hitchcock, marion (Box 23)
        - Home equity conversion (Box 23)
        - Homeless Program (Box 23)
        - Homes for the Homeless (Box 23)
        - Housing Activities, James Benjamin, 1984 (Box 23)
        - Housing Authority Legal Issues, Benjamin (Box 23)
        - Housing Conference, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Housing legislation (Box 23)
        - Housing Start reports, 1984 (Box 23)
        - Housing market study (Box 23)
        - Housing Task Force, Blue ribbon committee (Box 23)
        - Housing, 2000 (Box 23)
        - Housing Trust Fund (Box 23)
        - HUD correspondence (Box 23)
        - HUD, Boston, Regional General Inspection audit (Box 23)
        - Human services, 1986 (Box 23)